[
    {   "id":1,
        "Question":"When did the first world cup occur?",
        "a":"1932",
        "b":"1940",
        "c":"1950",
        "d":"1939",
        "answer":"1932"
    },
    {   "id":2,
        "Question":"Who is the current coach for Chelsea?",
        "a":"Mourinho",
        "b":"Lampard",
        "c":"Pep",
        "d":"Pele",
        "answer":"Lampard"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "Question":"Which country has won many World Cup Trophies?",
        "a":"Italy",
        "b":"German",
        "c":"Brazil",
        "d":"France",
        "answer":"Brazil"
    },
    {   "id":4,
        "Question":"Which is the capital city of Morrocco?",
        "a":"Djamena",
        "b":"Niamey",
        "c":"Rabat",
        "d":"Casablanca",
        "answer":"Rabat"
    },
    {   "id":5,
        "Question":"Which is the capital city of Spain?",
        "a":"Barcelona",
        "b":"Madrid",
        "c":"Lisbon",
        "d":"Rome",
        "answer":"Madrid"
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "Question":"Who scored the wining goal in the 2010 World Cup at the finals?",
        "a":"Morata",
        "b":"Villa",
        "c":"Fabregas",
        "d":"Iniesta",
        "answer":"Iniesta"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "Question":"Who discovered the force of gravity?",
        "a":"Einstein",
        "b":"Newton",
        "c":"Byles",
        "d":"Charlse",
        "answer":"Newton"
    },
    {   "id":8,
        "Question":"Who was the father of Jacob in the Bible?",
        "a":"Abraham",
        "b":"Isaac",
        "c":"Lot",
        "d":"David",
        "answer":"Isaac"
    },
    {   "id":9,
        "Question":"How many verses are there in the Holy Bible?",
        "a":"16,345",
        "b":"20,300",
        "c":"31,102",
        "d":"21,349",
        "answer":"31,102"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "Question":"How many people enter the Ark in the Bible?",
        "a":"5",
        "b":"6",
        "c":"2",
        "d":"8",
        "answer":"8"
    }
]